https://dreamtheater.net/privacy-policy/

PRIVACY POLICYThis Privacy Policy (“Privacy Policy”) governs the manner in which YTSE JAMS INC. (the “Company,” “we,” “us”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (“User, “you, or “your”) of the dreamtheater.net website (“Website” or “Site). This Privacy Policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by the Company. By accessing, using this Site or providing Personal Information to us, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy and all applicable laws.
When using the Site, you may find links to other websites, apps and services, or tools that enable you to share information with other websites, apps and services. The Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of these other websites, apps and services and we recommend that you review the privacy policies of each of these websites, apps or services before use.
We may revise the Privacy Policy at any time and you should visit this page periodically to review the Terms. We reserve the right to update or modify these terms at any time without prior notice. Your use of the Site following any such change constitutes your agreement be bound by the Privacy Policy as changed.
Personal Information We Collect
In order to fulfill purchases or provide services to you, we may require you to provide certain information to us. Common items may include, but are not limited to, your name, address, phone number, e-mail address and credit card number (“Personal Information”). By providing Personal Information to us, you are agreeing to allow us to utilize this Personal Information to complete all transactions you request through this Website and to disclose that information and details of all such transactions to the Company, our subsidiaries, affiliates and any necessary payment processors. We use standard commercial practices for keeping such data confidential, but there is no guarantee that such practices will prevent the disclosure or further distribution of such data beyond the Company.
How We Use Your Personal Information
We use the Personal Information that we collect about you for the following purposes:
To operate and maintain your account and to provide you with access to the Website and use of the any services that you may request from time to time. Your email address and password are used to identify you when you sign into the Website.
To provide you with technical support.
To respond to you about any comment or inquiry you have submitted.
To prevent or take action against activities that are, or may be, in breach of our Terms and Conditions or of applicable law.
We use your month and year of birth to enable age restrictions.
To send you important information regarding the Site, changes to our terms, conditions and policies and other administrative information.
To complete and fulfill your purchase, including to process your payments, have your order delivered to you, communicate with you regarding your purchase and provide you with related customer service.
To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.
To allow you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions and to administer these activities.
To facilitate social sharing functionality.
As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
How Your Personal Information Is Shared
We will not share your Personal Information with any third party, except as described in this Privacy Policy. There are circumstances where we may need to share some of the Personal Information we collect about you or which you provide to us for the purposes set out above – these circumstances are as follows:
To our third-party service providers who provide services such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, order fulfillment, information technology and related infrastructure provision, customer service, email delivery, auditing services and other similar services.
To third-party sponsors of sweepstakes, contests and similar promotions.
To identify you to anyone to whom you send messages through the Site.
By you, on message boards, chat, profile pages, blogs and other services to which you are able to post information and materials, if applicable. Please note that any Personal Information you post or disclose through these services will become public and may be available to visitors to the Site and to the general public. We urge you to be very careful when deciding to disclose your Personal Information, or any other information, on the Site.
We will disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that we are permitted or required to do so by law, including in response to a court order, subpoena or other legal demand or request.
We may disclose your Personal Information if we feel this is necessary in order to protect or defend our legitimate rights and interests, or those of our users, employees, directors or shareholders, and/or to ensure the safety and security of the Company.
In the context of a business transfer: We may transfer your Personal Information to any person or company that acquires all or substantially all of the assets or business of the Company, or on a merger of our business, or in the event of our insolvency.
As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.
Other Information We May Collect
We may also collect any information that does not reveal your specific identity or does not directly relate to an individual, such as browser information, information collected through cookies, pixel tags and other technologies, demographic information, other information provided by you, and aggregated information (“Other Information”).
How We Collect Other Information
We and our third-party service providers may collect Other Information in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to:
Through Your Browser or Device: Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your device, such as your Media Access Control (MAC) address, computer type (Windows or Macintosh), screen resolution, operating system version, device manufacturer and model, language and Internet browser type and version. We use this information to ensure that the Site functions properly.
Cookies: Cookies are pieces of information stored directly on the computer that you are using. Cookies allow us to collect information such as browser type, time spent on the Site, pages visited, language preferences and other anonymous traffic data. We and our service providers use the information for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to display information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while visiting the Site, as well as for online tracking purposes. We also use cookies to gather statistical information about the use of the Site in order to continually improve its design and functionality, understand how it is used and assist us with resolving questions about it. Cookies further allow us to select which of our content, advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are on the Site. We may also use cookies in online advertising to track responses to our advertisements.
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows you to automatically decline cookies or be given the choice of declining or accepting the transfer to your computer of a particular cookie (or cookies) from a particular site. You may also wish to refer to http://www.allaboutcookies.org. If you choose to decline cookies, you may experience some inconvenience in your use of the Site, and some or all of the features, functionality and promotions available through the Site may not be available to you.
We may use Google Analytics, which uses cookies and other, similar technologies to collect information about Site use anonymously and reports website trends, without identifying individual visitors. We also use an enhancement to Google Analytics called “Demographics and Interest Reporting,” through which Google provides us with information about Site users’ demographics (e.g., age, gender) and interests. This information, which Google may collect by tracking a user’s behaviour across third-party websites, helps us to learn more about our users. You can learn about Google’s practices in connection with this enhanced tracking and opt out of it by visiting http://www.google.com/settings/ads or by downloading the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on, available at https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
Pixel Tags and Similar Technologies: Pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) may be used in connection with some Site pages and HTML-formatted email messages to, among other things, track the actions of Site users and email recipients, measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about Site usage and response rates.
IP Address: Your IP Address is a number that is automatically assigned to the computer that you are using by your Internet Service Provider. An IP Address may be identified and logged automatically in our server log files whenever a user visits the Site, along with the time of the visit and the page(s) that were visited. We use IP Addresses for purposes such as calculating Site usage levels, helping diagnose server problems and administering the Site.
From You: We collect other information, such as your preferred means of communication, when you voluntarily provide it. Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you.
By Aggregating Information: Aggregated Personal Information does not personally identify you (for example, we may aggregate Personal Information to calculate the percentage of our users who have a particular telephone area code).
How We Use and Disclose Other Information
We may use and disclose Other Information for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. If we are required to treat Other Information as Personal Information under applicable law, then, in addition to the uses listed in the How We Collect Other Information section above, we may use and disclose Other Information for all the purposes for which we use and disclose Personal Information. In some instances, we may combine Other Information with Personal Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.
Third-Party Sites
This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the privacy, information or other practices of any third parties, including any third party operating any site to which this Site contains a link. The inclusion of a link on the Site does not imply endorsement of the linked site by us or by our affiliates.
Security
We use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure, please immediately notify us in accordance with the Contact Us section below.
Posted Content
If you are under 18 and a registered Site user, you may ask us to remove content or information that you have posted to the Site by writing to us via the form at [insert contact email]. Please note that your request does not ensure complete or comprehensive removal of the content or information, as, for example, some of your content may have been reposted by another user.
Choices and Access
We give you choices regarding our use and disclosure of your Personal Information for marketing purposes. You may opt out from:
Receiving Marketing Emails From Us: If you no longer want to receive marketing emails from us, you may opt out of receiving them by following the instructions contained in each such email. If you opt out, we may still send you important administrative messages.
We will try to comply with your request(s) as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that if you opt out as described above, we will not be able to remove your Personal Information from the databases of our affiliates or unaffiliated third parties with which we have already shared your Personal Information.
How You Can Access, Change or Suppress Your Personal Information
If you would like to review, correct, update, suppress, delete or otherwise limit our use of the Personal Information you have provided to us, you may access your online profile and other personal details through the Site, so that you can update them yourself. You can also do it by contacting us in writing at contact@crystalspotlight.com
In your request, please make clear what information you would like to have changed, whether you would like to have your Personal Information suppressed from our database or otherwise let us know what limitations you would like to put on our use of your Personal Information. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. For your protection, we may only implement requests with respect to the Personal Information associated with the email address you use to send us your request, and we may need to verify your identity before implementing your request.
Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to your request. There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.
Retention Period
We will retain your Personal Information for the period necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this Privacy Policy unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law.
Use of Site By Children
We do not collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13). We are committed to protecting children’s privacy.
Jurisdictional Issues
The Site is controlled and operated by us from the United States and is not intended to subject us to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, country or territory other than that of the United States.
Cross-Border Transfer
Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and, by using the Site, you consent to the transfer of information to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country.
Sensitive Information
We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., Social Security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health or criminal background) on or through the Site or otherwise to us.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us via contact@crystalspotlight.com. Because email communications are not always secure, please do not include credit card or other sensitive information in your messages to us.
Site © 2017 YTSE JAMS INC. unless otherwise noted. All rights reserved.
